amen amen
happy Sabbath everyone
um if you've been blessed uh by the
service thus far put that one in the
chat
um I'm still uh just uh really moved
from uh the Sabbath school today
and it's really been a High Sabbath the
the baby dedication the profession of
Faith uh the special music
um yeah that he was singing just now
um
and uh today we we this is our uh
evangelism Sabbath where we just share
doctrinal truths
um and we welcome anyone you know people
watching from everywhere we welcome
people who may not have heard of these
things before
um we're going to be talking about the
Rapture today
we're going to be talking about the
Rapture and
um it was interesting because and we're
going to pray but it was interesting
because this past week I saw an article
entitled Rapture anxiety
and the article was talking about how
many Christians suffer from this Rapture
anxiety
um and and this teaching of the Rapture
you know
as it goes uh some people will be taken
some people are going to be left behind
to go through a horrible time of trouble
so I decided for our evangelism Sabbath
uh which is every fourth Sabbath last
week we were not live so I'm doing it
this week instead
um we decided that we would do the
Rapture and so this is going to be a
pretty straightforward and simple study
um if you know people that you believe
need to hear this message please go
ahead and hit that invite or invite them
share this link with them
um and this is going to clear up some
confusion about this teaching that many
call The Rapture
um so with that said uh let's go ahead
and begin with the word of prayer and
then we're going to get into the
messaging we're just going to kind of
move through this really rapidly but
there's some very powerful things I want
you to see and understand
um as we go this through this
presentation so let's go ahead and pray
Heavenly Father we ask Lord that you
bless us as we uh open your word Lord
please speak uh please teach please
instruct and above all Lord please
convict this we pray in Jesus name amen
and amen all right so we're going to go
to the screen Rapture anxiety the
question is is the rapture biblical is
the rapture as it is popularly taught
biblical
um there are three main points that I
want you to pull from this study today
and I will let you know the points after
I conclude them okay
so uh the first thing we want to know is
this uh some people say the Rapture some
people say the second coming and many
people believe that the Rapture is
different from the second coming there's
a Rapture there's uh this seven year
period of tribulation and then the
second coming
um
so I'm going to I'm not going to speak
on this
so-called seven year tribulation uh
subject today that's going to be for
another time but what I want to show you
will will definitely leave you asking
questions well wait a minute where what
where did seven year thing come from
um and I'm going to suggest to you
uh in fact I'm not gonna I just want to
take you through and then I'll make this
suggestion later regarding the seven
year uh this seven year Theory put a one
in the chat if you guys can hear me
someone is saying there's no sound
um might be on your side but just let me
see that you guys are hearing me well
put a one in the chat if you can hear me
all right okay excellent excellent okay
so let's go ahead and Jump Right In I
want to go to the screen and let's go
ahead and look at our first text
uh Matthew 24 and verse 36 onward and
this is one of the most popular verses
used to teach uh the quote-unquote
Rapture
um and you'll see as I read the text the
Bible says in Matthew 24 36 but of that
day and hour knoweth no man no not the
angels of heaven but my father only
but as the days of Noah were social also
the coming of the son of man be
verse 38.
for as in the days that were before the
flood they were eating and drinking and
marrying and giving in marriage until
the day that Noah entered into the ark
and knew not until the flood came and
took them all away
social also the coming of the son of man
be
then shall to be in the field the one
shall be taken and the other left
two women shall be grinding at the Mill
the one shall be taken and the other
left
so this is uh obviously where you know
popular movies like Left Behind the Left
Behind series uh is taken from this is
the verse and it clearly says here that
in the day of Jesus Christ it'll be like
the days of Noah
um one will be taken one will be left
and many people look at this as the
Rapture where some people are taken up
to heaven
um and the those who are not prepared
for Christ are left behind
so I'm going to ask a question
this is a test question according to the
text
um
do you want to be taken or left
according to the text do you want to be
taken or left so go ahead and put that
in the chat taken if you want to be
taken or left if you want to be left
which one do you think
what group of people do you want to be
in
okay so
um some of you want to be in the taking
group and some of you are saying you
want to be in the left group why the
confusion why the confusion
um somebody said I want to be left
behind that almost sounds like what you
want to be left but what
um
so let's let's take a look at what the
text says again I want to go back to the
screen and let me just let me just come
back here so some of you are putting
left some of you are putting taken let's
read it again 1924 38 for as in the days
that were before the flood they were
eating and drinking marrying and giving
in marriage until the day that Noah
entered into the ark and knew not until
the flood came
and
took them all away
now let me ask a question again
how many of you want to be taken
how many of you want to be left
note that the text
took the the text says that the flood
came and took them all away so who's the
all here is it Noah and his family or is
it the world
yes yes it was it was the Wicked that
were taken away
well what does it mean that they were
taken away very good some of y'all are
getting this now oh wait a minute I
don't want to be taken away I want to be
left man that's opposite from the movie
though
that's opposite from the Left Behind
series because the Left Behind series
those that are left behind
are the are the wicked ones and those
that are taken are the Righteous but the
text says that it was the Wicked that
were taken away
all right come on let the best way for
us to figure this out is to go back to
the story of Noah
and you remember in the flood uh Noah
builds the ark and then the flood comes
and notice what the text says Genesis 7
verse 21 and All Flesh died that moved
upon the Earth both the fowl and of
cattle and of Beast and of every
creeping thing that creepeth upon the
Earth and every man
all in whose nostrils was the Breath of
Life all that was in the dry land died
and every living substance was destroyed
which was upon the face of the ground
both Man and Cattle and creeping things
and the fowls of the heaven and they
were destroyed from the earth and Noah
only what's that next word you guys Noah
only what
remained
remained what alive give me another word
to remain put another word in the chat
for remain for me please
what's another word for remit what other
word could we use in the place of
remained alive
yes Robert yes left left they were left
alive so I want you to note then being
taken is synonymous let let we need to
break this down y'all being taken was
synonymous with what
death
all in whose nostrils was the breath of
life and all that was in the dry land
died so being taken means they were
destroyed they died while being left
meant Left Alive remained alive now let
me ask you a question
according to the to the NOAA account
was there anyone
alive that was not in the ark
was there anyone alive that was not in
the ark
no no no no
if you were in the ark you lived if you
were not in the ark you died
there was no second opportunity there
was no seven years waiting for another
boat or seven weeks waiting for another
boat there was only one vote
in other words once the Noah's door was
shut he that was filthy would remain
filthy still and he that was righteous
would remain righteous still there was
no changing there was no opportunity for
those outside the ark for them to now
get their lives together and the popular
teaching of the Rapture as it is
understood by many people is that those
who are left behind have this second
opportunity to get it right with God but
Beloved the very example Jesus uses
there is no such example of a second
chance
once the door is shut those who are in
remain alive and those who are out are
taken in death
we can see the same thing
we can see the same thing if we look at
the account in Luke likewise also as it
was in the days of lot they did eat they
drank they bought they sold they planted
they build it but the same day that lot
went out of Sodom it rained fire and
brimstone from heaven and destroyed some
of them
While others were left behind to go
through a time of trouble no no no no
that's not what it says and destroyed
them what all
even thus shall it be in the day when
the son of man is revealed the revealing
of the son of man
now I want you to know here that the
Bible
speaks of the coming of the son of man
as a singular event
in other words
there's not two second comings of the
Lord there is only one second coming of
the Lord
if you want to call that the Rapture
that's fine if you want to call it the
second coming that's fine but the
Rapture is the very same thing as the
second coming the Bible speaks of this
as a singular event not multiple events
not Christ coming secretly and invisibly
one time and then him coming again a few
years later visibly for everyone to see
there's no place in the Bible where
Christ is described as coming secretly
where no one sees him and we're going to
get to that Thief
text in a moment
so just follow me here
I want you to notice the next text which
is the next let's move to the next
portion which is this question when does
this happen
when is it that Jesus comes again and
all who are in him are saved or remain
alive while those who are not in him
because he is our Ark those who are not
in Christ are destroyed when does that
happen well according to the Bible
first Thessalonians 4 15 says this for
this we say unto you by the word of the
Lord that we which are alive and what's
that next word right there everyone
remain notice the consistency Paul is
speaking about the second coming here
and he's saying listen we which are
alive and remain meaning we remained
alive at the coming of Christ
we which are alive and remain unto the
coming of the Lord shall not prevent
them which are asleep those that died in
Christ watch what the text says for the
Lord himself shall descend from heaven
with a shout with the voice of the
Archangel and with the Trump of God and
the dead in Christ shall rise first
watch this then we which are alive and
remain there it goes again alive and
remain remain alive those of us that are
left that survive the second coming of
Christ shall be caught up together with
them in the clouds to meet the Lord in
the air and so shall we ever be with the
Lord now I want you to note something
I'm going to quote this text a little
bit later
but notice that the Bible does not say
that Jesus is coming down
to the ground
it says that we are going to be caught
up together with them in the clouds
to be with the Lord remember Jesus said
in John chapter 14 I go to prepare a
place for you and if I go to prepare a
place I will come again and receive you
that where I am there you may be with me
also
what Jesus says look
I'm going to having to prepare a place
for you and I'm going to come back
didn't say I'm gonna come back twice I'm
gonna come back that's the second coming
and receive you that where I am that's
Heaven There will you be also keep that
in mind because I'm going to show you
something here shortly so here's the
next question when is this Trump when is
this this uh when does Jesus descend
with the Trump of god notice again the
text
First Corinthians 15 51. it says behold
I show you a mystery we shall not all
sleep but we should all be changed
meaning some of us will remain alive at
the second coming of Jesus while many
will die but also watch this
the wicked who are alive at the second
coming of Christ will be destroyed by
the brightness of his coming
so we which are alive and remain those
inside the ark are inside Jesus are the
ones that are alive and remain those
outside of Jesus are destroyed there's
no second opportunity for them just as
there was no second opportunity for
those outside the Ark in Noah's day
so notice what it goes on to say
we shall all be changed in a moment in
the twinkling of an eye at the last
Trump for the trumpet shall sound and
the dead shall be raised Incorruptible
and we shall be changed for this
corruptible must put on incorruption and
this Mortal must put on immortality so
when this corruptable shall have put on
incorruption and this Mortal shall have
put on immortality then shall be brought
to pass the same that is written death
is swallowed up in Victory so here we
clearly see that the last Trump is the
very last event it is the time when
death itself will be destroyed meaning
this is the second coming
there's not two different comings of the
Lord
the Rapture is the second coming the
second coming is the rapture Rapture
simply means the catching up it's one
event that's the first thing I need you
to understand it is one event notice the
text Matthew chapter 24 and verse 30.
and then shall appear the sign of the
son of man in heaven and then shall all
the tribes of the earth mourn and they
shall see the son of man well that marks
out the son of man coming invisibly
people don't see him hey what happened I
Think Jesus came because people just
disappeared no no no no the Bible says
that the tribes of the Earth shall see
the son of man coming in what the Clouds
Of Heaven with power and great glory and
he shall send his angels with a great
sound of a trumpet you guys all these
verses are paralleling with each other
they saw gathered together his elect
from the Four Winds from one end of
Heaven to the other
notice again with me
Revelation chapter 1 verse 7 behold he
cometh with clouds so he knows the same
event he's coming with the clouds
we know the same event every eye sees
him and they also which pierced him and
all the kingdoms of the Earth shall wail
because of him so the first point I want
you to understand is very simply this
there is no two-stage second coming of
Jesus
it is simply the the second coming of
Christ
if you're with me so far put a one in
the chat
there is no seven years separating an
invisible coming of Christ from a
visible coming of Christ it is simply
the second coming of Christ or if you
want to say the Rapture the catching up
okay Point number one down we got two
more points to go very simple two more
points to go and uh here's what we need
to understand the next thing I need you
to understand this is crucial is that
before the coming of Christ occurs there
is something hugely significant that
must happen
what is that thing
notice with me second Thessalonians and
that one and two shouldn't be there in
front of the simply second Thessalonians
chapter 2 verse one
and it says this now we beseech you
Brethren by the coming of our Lord Jesus
Christ and by our gathering together
unto him right so again one one event is
not secretive every eye sees it it's
like lightning
every eye sees it everybody knows it no
one's gonna be like hey I heard Jesus
came not every eye shall see it
so that's what he's talking about in
verse one he says listen they see uh we
beseech you Brethren by the coming of
our Lord Jesus Christ and by gathering
together into him that you be not soon
shaken in mind or troubled by or
troubled neither by Spirit nor by word
nor by letter asked from us as that the
day of Christ is at hand in other words
Paul is saying listen
the day of the Lord is coming but I
don't want you to get confused and think
that it's coming just like that because
something must happen before that day
comes and notice what it says
let no man deceive you by any means
for that day shall not come
except there come a falling away and
that the man of sin be revealed
the Son of Perdition now something very
interesting here well by the way let me
finish reading who opposes and exalted
himself above all that is called God or
that is worshiped so that he now what's
these next two words
as God
as God please remember those words as
God
sitteth in the temple of God showing
himself that he is God so what we're
seeing here
is that
before the second coming of Christ
it will be preceded by another event let
me let me let me show you something so
that word revealed that we saw the man
of sin shall be revealed the the word
revealed here let me just show you this
is the Greek for the world of revealed
it is Apocalypto
apocalypse
the revealing the revelation
why is that word so significant
The Book of Revelation
The Book of Revelation the revelation of
Jesus Christ
the revelation of Jesus Christ is the
second coming of Christ where he is
revealed
to all Humanity every eye sees him it is
the Revelation the the literal
revelation of Jesus Christ is the second
coming put a one in the chat if you get
that
what Paul is telling us here
is that before the revelation of Jesus
Christ occurs there is going to be a
counterfeit Revelation put a one in the
chat and you caught what I just said
there's going to be a counterfeit
revelation
this this this being called
the man of sin
the Son of Perdition who will set
himself up as God
so so let's let's talk about this term
Son of Perdition what is this term Son
of Perdition right what does that term
mean we just read it let me go back to
it uh um let no man deceive you by any
means for that dayson.com except they're
coming Falling Away first and that man
of sin
be revealed Apocalypto
the Revelation and then it says the Son
of Perdition so where else in the Bible
is this term Son of Perdition used well
if you go to John 17 verse 12 the Bible
says while I was with them in the world
I kept them them in thy name this is
Jesus speaking
those that thou gave me gave gave us me
I have kept and none of them is lost
but the Son of Perdition that the
scriptures might be fulfilled so I ask
you a question who was the son of
perdition
who was a son of perdition
the son of perdition
who was it that betrayed Jesus who was
it that when Jesus said I've lost none
of them except the son of tradition who
was that
y'all got it that was Judas that was
Judas that was Judas right Judas is
called the son of perdition
so Jesus saying oh Judas is going to
come again no no no no no no no no no
why is Jude is called the Son of
Perdition anyone know why Judas was
called the son of perdition
let me tell you why he was called the
Son of Perdition come with me to John
chapter 6 verse 70. Jesus answered them
have I have not I chosen you 12 and one
of you is a what
yes one of you is a devil he spake of
Judas Iscariot the son of Simon for he
it he it was that should betray him
being one of the twelves so Judas is
called the Son of Perdition because he's
described as a devil
now is Judas the ultimate Son of
Perdition let me say this way is Judas
the ultimate devil
yes or no
no no no no
Judas is not the ultimate devil
and Judas is not coming back at the end
of time before Jesus comes again
the ultimate devil you guys
is devil
the ultimate devil is the devil now you
know I don't want to get too far into
this because
the devil Works through
instrumentalities and at the end of time
he's going to be working through a very
specific instrumentality an organization
but we're not going to get into that
right now what I want you to understand
here is that while the devil is working
through that organization the ultimate
man of sin the ultimate Son of Perdition
is Satan himself let me break this down
for you just a little bit further
because I need you to understand this
Watch What Happens Watch What Happens in
Luke chapter 22 verse 3. so remember
after Judas takes the SOP then the Bible
says then
entered Satan into Judas named Iscariot
being of the number of the twelve so
what happened here Judas or Satan
entered Judas so what does that mean
what's actually happening here what is
this picture
pink for us of of Satan entering Judas
all right
I'm not going to I need to break this
down to you from scripture so let me
just show you okay we're gonna go to
First Timothy chapter 3 verse 16.
First Timothy chapter 3 verse 16 the
Bible says and without controversy great
is the mystery of godliness
put that in a chat for me mystery of
godliness what is the mystery of
godliness God was manifest in the what
In the Flesh all right the mystery of
godliness you guys is God manifest In
the Flesh in the person of Jesus Christ
are y'all with me
God was manifesting the flesh this is
the mystery of godliness what you have
happening in Judas is Satan being
manifested in the flesh that's the
that's the type if you will can I say
that that's the type Judas is a type of
the son of perdition and what does that
mean the Son of Perdition he's the son
of perdition because Satan has entered
into flesh
put a one in the chat if you get what
I'm saying Satan has entered into flesh
so now we want to ask the question what
is this what's going to happen at the
End of Time Pastor what are you saying
who is this man of sin who is the son of
tradition that's going to produce this
counterfeit Apocalypto come on y'all
that's going to produce this counterfeit
coming of Jesus Christ before Jesus
Christ actually comes well let's go to
the text
not is going to jump out to y'all watch
this second Thessalonians right second
Thessalonians chapter 2 verse 7.
for the mystery of iniquity does already
work
only he who now let us will let until he
be taken out of the way and then shall
that Wicked capital W which could be
revealed whom the Lord shall consume
with the spirit of his mouth and shall
destroy with the brightness of his
coming even him whose coming is after
the working of Satan with all power and
signs and lying wonders and with all
deceivableness of unrighteousness in
them that perish because they receive
not the love of the truth that they
might be saved I need you to understand
something here
if the mystery of godliness
is God manifest in the flesh
then the mystery of iniquity
are y'all catching this
the mystery of iniquity
must be
Satan
manifest in the flesh
Satan taking on human form foreign
counterfeiting the second coming of
Jesus Christ
this is ultimately who will sit in the
temple of God showing himself that he is
God and is this something new no because
if you go back to the book of Isaiah
chapter 14 guess what you see speaking
of Lucifer the Bible says how art thou
fallen from Heaven o Lucifer
Sun of the morning how art thou cut down
to the ground which did sweeten the
Nations for thou has said in thine
Hearts I will Ascend into heaven I will
exalt my throne above the stars of God I
will sit also upon the Mount of the
congregation in the size of the north I
will Ascend above the heights of the
clouds I will be like the most high
put a one in the chat y'all if this is
making sense to you
in heaven Satan wanted to sit in the
place of God well it only makes sense
that just before Jesus comes again the
second time Satan is going to seek to
impersonate to counterfeit the
Apocalypse
now why is he doing this why is he
trying to counterfeit the Apocalypse
well the answer is very simple
who's he trying to deceive
let me ask it this way who would be
happy about the second coming of Jesus
non-believers
atheists Skeptics
no no no no no they're not the ones that
want Jesus to come who wants Jesus to
come
Christians
Christians Want Jesus to come
so who do you think Satan is coming to
deceive if he's if he's putting on this
whole performance hey I'm Jesus who is
he ultimately trying to deceive he must
be trying to deceive Christians which
beloved helps you to understand that
Christians will be here
on Earth they will not be raptured away
to escape persecute they will be here on
Earth as Satan seeks to counterfeit the
second coming of Jesus and tries to
gather in Christians to worship Him
and Beloved the only way we can avoid
this deception is by knowing what the
Bible says about the second coming of
Jesus
that's why the world isn't so much
that's why the Christian world is in so
much confusion right now about the
Rapture oh pre-trib post-trib Mitch all
this stuff when the Bible does not teach
anything about this seven year the Bible
teaches of one second coming that's why
it's called the second coming
the Bible teaches that when Jesus comes
those who are righteous will be
righteous still and those who are filthy
will be filthy still and just as in the
days of Noah just as in the days of lot
the wicked will be taken away destroyed
while the righteous Left Alive
if y'all would be so far I'll put one in
the chat we also just learned that
before the second coming of Christ there
will be a counterfeit a counterfeit
apocalypse by Satan himself in which he
is attempting to deceive if possible the
very elect
that means the elect are still on Earth
guys
he's attended to see the very elect now
why is he seeking to impersonate Christ
how is he planning to deceive the very
elect let's that this is our last
question
this is our last question let's go to
John chapter 14. and let me show you
something else here John chapter 14 John
chapter 14 beginning with verse one let
not your heart be troubled Jesus said
you believe in God believe also in me in
my father's house are many mansions if
it were not so I would have told you I
go to prepare a place for you and if I
go and prepare prepare a place for you I
will come again and receive you unto
myself
that where I am there you may be also
it's very important to understand this
um friends
when Jesus comes again he's coming for
the purpose of receiving Us in the place
that he now is
in other words he's not coming to set up
a kingdom on Earth that does not happen
until a later time we'll get into that
in a moment but when he comes again the
second time the reason we are meeting
him in the clouds in the air is because
he's taking us to be where he is
I will receive unto myself that where I
am where I am where is he in heaven
right now there will you be also
Revelation 20 Bears us out
in Revelation 20 beginning with verse 1
and I saw an angel come down from heaven
having the key of the bottomless pit and
a great chain in his hand and he laid
hold on the dragon that old servant
which is the devil and bound him a
thousand years that's that's what it's
called the Millennium reading on and
cast them into the bottom of this pit
and shut him up and set a seal upon him
that he should deceive the Nations no
more till the Thousand Years should be
fulfilled and after that he must be
loosed a little season so let me break
this down very quickly no no let's keep
reading and I saw Thrones and they sat
upon them and judgment was given unto
them and I saw the souls of them that
were beheaded for the witness of Jesus
and for the word of God and which had
not worshiped the Beast not in His image
neither had received his Mark upon their
foreheads or in their hands and they
lived and reigned with Christ A Thousand
Years meaning listen carefully meaning
they come to life
all at the same time because they reign
with Christ a thousand years now we just
learned that when Christ says you will
be with me where I am where is that
it's in heaven
so watch this guys
the righteous dead are caught up in the
clouds and we which are alive and remain
those that are Left Alive because
they're in Christ are caught up with
them in the clouds what does Jesus do
when we're in the clouds he takes us to
heaven to be with him for a thousand
years
well what about the wicked where are
they ah what happened in the days of
Noah the wicked were all taken away that
means they are destroyed they die at the
second coming of Jesus so where where
does this leave planet Earth who's on
Earth
nobody's on Earth
the devil is bound here on this Earth
while the righteous are in heaven and
the wicked are dead upon the Earth
that's why the Earth experiences a
thousand years of Peace not because the
nations are like ah let's all get along
now no the nations of the righteous are
in heaven and the nations of the wicked
are dead on the Earth
remember there's only two groups as it
was in the days of Noah as it was in the
days of lot it's the same thing
why is this important to understand
here's why
let me keep let me let me read another
text here watch this but the rest of the
Dead live not again until the Thousand
Years we're finished this is the first
resurrection blessed and holy is he that
has part in the First Resurrection on
such the second deck has no power but
they shall be Priests of God and of
Christ and shall reign with him a
thousand years so the text clearly tells
us that this is the first resurrection
when does that Resurrection happen it
happens at the second coming of Jesus
Christ at the last Trump when the dead
are raised Incorruptible and the
righteous are caught up together with
him to meet them in the air this is what
this is what kicks off the millennium
okay
now please follow along here I need you
to see this just just for just for
reference
Isaiah 24 19. speaking about the
condition of the earth during the
millennium
this is the secondary application of
this text many of you may not understand
what that means but let me just read it
Isaiah 24 19 the Earth is utterly broken
down the Earth is clean dissolved the
Earth is moved exceedingly the Earth
shall reel to and fro like a drunkard
and shall be removed like a cottage and
the transgression thereof shall be heavy
upon it it shall fall and not rise again
verse 21 and this shall come to pass in
that day that the Lord shall punish the
host of the high ones that are on high
and the kings of the earth upon the
Earth they shall be gathered together as
prisoners are gathered in the pit ah
remember that Satan is bound in a
bottomless pit where are the wicked
they're in that same pit but where is
that pit it's upon the Earth
it's the grave they shall be shut up in
the prison and after many days what are
those many days after 1 000 years they
shall be visited that's why the Bible
says the rest of the Dead that is the
wicked did not live again until the
thousand years were finished
are y'all with me so far
let's keep moving put a one in the chat
if you're with me so far
I want you to notice what the text says
next second Peter chapter 3 verse 10.
the Bible says here but the day of the
Lord will come as a thief in the night
now this is the text that people use to
say ah see Jesus comes like a thief but
watch this guys
the coming of the thief is not meant to
describe secrecy it's meant to describe
surprise
no one expects a thief to come and why
does the thief come in the night if
you're a thief
you would want to break into a house
in the daytime people are gone they're
at work
if you're a thief coming into the house
at night you're coming in to do damage
you're coming in to hurt people
because everybody's home
but notice what happens in the uh so
when Jesus comes it'll be a surprise
it's not that it'll be secret it'll be a
surprise and how do we know it's not
going to be a secret because it says in
the which the heavens shall pass away
with a great noise and the elements
shall melt with fervent Heat and the
Earth also and the works of therein
shall be burned up that's why the Earth
is in a desolate State that's why the
Earth is in a place is in a place where
it is uninhabitable
so what is Satan trying to do when he
comes before the second coming of Christ
he's coming
pretending to set up
a millennium
a time of Peace look everyone I'm Jesus
and I'm here to usher in a thousand
years of peace all of you who love me
come serve me come bow down before me
are y'all with me
so very good
um I see here uh that uh uh I'm not
gonna call I'm just gonna say uh there's
someone saying well what about Isaiah
when the Bible says in the last days the
mountain of the Lord's Temple will be
established as the highest of the
mountains and it will be exalted in
other words the mountain is good the the
mountain of the Lord is going to be
established on Earth well let me just
show you when that is and you know what
I don't have the I don't have to touch
my screen but I just want to refer you
to Revelation chapter 21.
Revelation 20 we just read is about the
Millennium the 1000 years in Revelation
21 at the end of the 1000 Years John
sees the New Jerusalem the Holy Mountain
coming down down from God out of heaven
and where is that Jerusalem coming to
it's coming to the Earth
did you all catch that this happens at
the end of the 1000 years
thank you Rick for putting the text up
there and watch this now notice what the
text says in Revelation 21 it says and
the temple of God is with men
and God shall be with them now remember
this watch this
what did Jesus say in John 14 I'm going
to prepare a place for you that where I
am there you may be with me
I'm taking you to heaven but after the 1
000 years the temple of God is with men
God now comes down to earth and makes
his home among the inhabitants of the
Earth this is when Jerusalem becomes the
center of all praise that's one point
another point I need to bring up very
quickly and I'm going to move on okay
many of these verses that people use in
Isaiah and Jeremiah you heard me say
something just now which I'm glad I said
it remember you heard me say this is the
secondary application of Isaiah when I
was talking about how it points to the
Earth during the desolated state in the
millennium
many verses in Isaiah and Jeremiah and
Ezekiel
were verses talking about a kingdom that
God was going to set up on Earth if his
people were obedient to him
if his people were obedient to him if
they accepted Christ when he came
because that was all the prophecy was
pointed to Christ is coming and if you
accept Christ this nation is going to be
an amazing Nation you're going to be the
center the glory of the world people are
going to come to you and there's going
to be
they will understand
the beauty of the Gospel
you will beat your swords
into place you this this Kingdom will be
the light of the world the problem is
that these prophecies in Isaiah and
Jeremiah and Ezekiel were conditional
prophecies and because Jerusalem in
essence rejected the conditions of those
prophecies
those promises never came to pass
and so what we need to understand
beloved is that the 1 000 years of peace
on Earth is because the Earth is lying
desolate it's not because nations are
like Hey we're cool now we're getting
along and people are now converted that
is not in the Bible that's an incorrect
reading of the of the the Prophecies of
Jeremiah and Ezekiel and Isaiah
these promises of a New Jerusalem occur
at the end of the 1000 years that's why
the New Jerusalem is seen coming down
from heaven at the end of the 1000 years
it's not on Earth and then goes back up
to heaven at the end of the 1000 years
to come back down to Earth again no
Young
that's not how it works but I'm going to
keep moving on okay I'm going to keep
moving on and I want you to notice the
next text let's go let's go to
Revelation chapter 13. Revelation
chapter 13 13. speaking of this end time
power and this end time apocalypse the
Bible says he doeth great wonders so the
next Fire come down from heaven on the
earth and a side of men
and deceive with them that dwell on the
Earth by the means of those Miracles
which he had power to do in the sight of
the Beast saying to them that dwell on
the earth that they should make an image
to the Beast which had the wound by a
sword and did live and he had power to
give life unto the image of the Beast
that the image of the Beast should both
speak and cause that as many as would
not worship the image of the Beast
should be killed now why is it
significant why is it important
that we understand this concept about an
image of the Beast why is that important
to understand well here's why
The Book of Revelation is borrowing
language from The Book of Daniel well
let's see what happens in The Book of
Daniel you guys let's see what happens
in Daniel chapter 3 verse 1 the Bible
says nebuchadnezz of the king made an
image of gold whose height watch this
whose height
was three score qubits and the breadth
there were of six cubits
he set it up in the plains of dura in
the province of Babylon
then nebuchadnezz of the king sent
together the princes and I'm not going
to read all this you know what he's
about to do right he's about to tell
everyone that they have to bow down
before the image now what is this here
this is an image of a man
did y'all did y'all get what I just said
this is an image of a man Babylon the
king of Babylon sets up an image of a
man we can say this is a man of sin we
can say that
this man of sin Nebuchadnezzar is
commanding them to bow down to worship
this image
y'all need to follow me on this
okay he's he's commanding them to Bow
Down and Worship the image it's the
image of a man
who do you think this man is
counterfeiting
come on who do you think this image is
kind of this is pointing us right back
to Revelation chapter 13 where at the
end of time there's going to be an this
is not a literal image being set up it
is symbolic of something it is an image
of some it is it is symbolic of of
something satanic
but pretending to be like Christ
and I want you to watch what happens
here
I want you to watch what happens here
in fact let me go back here let me do
this real quick
so we know that this is an image of all
gold
and what's very interesting is if you go
to Revelation chapter 1 verse 12 and you
read about the description of Jesus it
says I turn to see the voice that's fake
with me and being turned I saw seven
golden candlesticks and in the midst of
the seven candlesticks one like the Son
of Man Clothing the Garment down to the
foot and gird about the patch with a
golden girl to watch this his head and
his hair were of pure wool what light
white wool and as white as snow and his
eyes were a flame of fire and his feet
like onto fine brass as if they burned
in a furnace and his voice as a sound of
many Waters
so some translations in fact I'm just
read the definition to you of what fine
brass is some metal like gold if not
more precious that is very interesting
because if if Jesus is here looking like
gold a golden man but over here over
there in Daniel you have this golden
image being set up
what did that golden image represent
the golden image as a man let me let me
listen carefully is not only a symbol of
the man of sin
the son of perdition
Satan who ultimately wants to worship
for himself but it also represents the
setting up of a kingdom
remember
just one chapter before this
Nebuchadnezzar is shown that his kingdom
is going to fall and it's going to fall
to Jesus
right Babylon is going to fall to meet a
Persia so he had a dream of an image of
a man head of gold chest on Silver
billion thousand brats legs of iron toes
of iron and clay and then a stone which
is Jesus destroys the image
Nebuchadnezzar is not happy with the
stream and so in the next chapter he
makes an image of all gold saying I've
set up my kingdom and this kingdom is
going to last forever like you know I
don't know a thousand years
this kingdom is Gonna Last Forever
come on y'all come on watch this watch
this so what happens what happens so the
image
Nebuchadnezzar commands the people to
worship the image right and I want you
to check out what happens so the people
fall down and says whosoever does not
fall down shall be shall the same hour
be cast into the midst of a burning
fiery furnace
everybody bows down right but now note
this
some of the people Nebuchadnezzar's uh
uh uh government people come to them and
say hey Nebuchadnezzar listen there are
certain Jews God's people whom thou has
set over their fears of the province of
Babylon Shadrach Meshach and Abednego
these men O King have not regarded thee
they serve not thy Gods nor worship the
golden image which thou has set up
please y'all let me break this down for
you
when Revelation borrows from Daniel
and it's saying look remember the image
in Daniel go back to that and study it
out
beloved these three Hebrews were present
in this
time where the image is being set up to
be worshiped as if it were God
and while everybody else is bowing down
there is a group of people who refuse to
Bow who refuse to acquiesce who refuse
to bend the knee beloved this is what
God is trying to tell us is going to
happen at the End of Time Satan is going
to come in before Christ pretending to
be Christ and command that everyone bow
down and many women but listen there are
many who are watching this program today
many who are hearing this for the first
time today and some even who are arguing
in the chat right now saying no no no
this is not true I've always been taught
this and you're trying to defend what
you believe is true and I get that I
understand that when you're hearing
something for the first time that is new
or even hearing it for the second or
third or fifth time yes you may want to
fight against it but listen to me
what God is trying to show us y'all
is that at the end of time there will be
a group of people who because of their
study of the word of God and because of
their love for Jesus have come into a
knowledge of this truth and have
accepted it so that when they see this
being come down and touch the ground
with his feet they're gonna be like wait
a minute no no no no no no no no no no
Jesus said when he comes again the
Saints are going to meet him in the
clouds
and we're going to be with him and reign
with him a thousand years with him where
he is a thousand years and so when they
see this this imposter this counterfeit
Apocalypto
they're going to be like we're not
bowing
they're going to pull that that story
from from Daniel chapter three Shadrach
me sucking Abednego they did not bow and
here we are not everybody else is bound
because everybody else thinks oh yeah
this is the Millennium this is what the
Bible talked about Jesus coming to set
his kingdom up on Earth and beloved
millions of Christians so-called
Christians will bow to this counterfeit
image simply because they refused
to ditch traditional teachings
they refused
or chose not to hear the truth of God's
word
this counterfeit Apocalypto this
counterfeit apocalypse this counterfeit
revealing of this man of sin this son of
perdition Satan manifests in the flesh
pretending to be Christ
will come saying the very thing that
many people are saying right now when
Jesus comes the Millennium is going to
be on the earth and so man think about
how many Christians are out there
waiting for the coming of Satan
not realizing
that's not
that's not Jesus
he's claiming to be Jesus
he's looking golden like Jesus
but that's not Jesus because Jesus is
not setting up his Millennial Temple
upon this Earth
and notice how these three Hebrews
respond then Nebuchadnezzar in israising
Fury commanded to bring Shadrach Meshach
and Abednego then they brought these men
before the King Nebuchadnezzar spake and
said unto them is it true oshadrach
Meshach and Abednego do you not serve my
gods nor worship the golden images I
have set up are you not going to
acquiesce that this is the millennial
kingdom are you look man everybody else
is bowing down why are you blaspheming
Jesus
why are you blaspheming Jesus by the way
this is what Jesus meant when he said
the time is coming where they that kill
you will think they're doing God's
service because listen to me beloved
listen to me fellow Baptist fellow
Pentecostal fellow catholic whatever you
are listen to me in this time when
everyone
and you're going not Jesus
that's a counterfeit
the other so-called Christian look at
you like how dare you blaspheme look at
the Miracles he's doing look at the
peace he's bringing upon her how dare
you blaspheme and you know the penalty
for blasphemy is
when Jesus says I'm coming to set up
this theocracy and now I'm ruling and
all the government is going to be based
upon my law
except it'll be a counterfeit law
it'll be a law that encourages people to
break the law of God instead of keep the
law of God listen y'all
the time is coming where they that kill
you will think they're doing it on
behalf of God
but they're not worshiping the true God
it's a counterfeit God
so these three men refused about arm
they refused to worship listen to what
it says now if you be ready at what time
you hear the sound of the corner the
flute the harp the side but the sultry
the dulcimer and all kinds of music You
Fall Down and Worship the images I have
made well but if you do not worship you
will be cast the same hour into the
midst of a burning fiery furnace and who
is that God that shall deliver you out
of my hands I need you to understand
beloved that God's people are going
through tribulation they will go through
tribulation and this study is setting
that out clearly
we are not careful to answer thee in
this matter if it be so our God whom we
serve is able to Deliver Us From The
Burning fiery furnace and he will
deliver us out of Van handle King but if
not
be it known unto you just be certain
just know that King
we will not serve thy God nor worship
the golden image which thou has set up
then was Nebuchadnezzar full of Fury and
the form of his Visage was changed
against sadrach Meshach and Abednego
therefore he's speaking commanded that
they should be that they should heat the
furnace seven times more than it would
want to be Heat
and they commanded that the most mighty
men that were in his army to bind
Shadrach Meshach and Abednego and to
cast them into the burning fiery furnace
these men were Bound in their coats
their holes in and their hats and other
garments and were cast into the midst of
the burning fiery furnace but watch this
oh no no no no come come these three men
sidetracked me so I can Letting Go fell
down in the midst of the burning fiery
furnace then Nebuchadnezzar the King was
astanied and Rose up in haste and spake
and said unto his counselors did not
recast three men Bound in the midst of
the fire then answer them and said O
King true O King and he answered and
said lo I see four men loose walking in
the midst of the fire and they have no
hurt and the form of the fourth is this
is like the Son of God y'all come on
somebody needs to say Amen
somebody needs to say Amen listen
people are worried I don't want to be in
a time of trouble I don't want to be
here for the tribulation God says listen
if you trust me
I will bring you through the fire I will
bring you through the flame the Son of
God the form of the fourth will
eventually come and deliver his people
and God says even if you have to die
look at Shadrach me suck and Abednego
they were like look we're willing to die
we love not our lives unto the death
Revelation 12 11 they overcame him by
the blood of the lamb and by the word of
their testimony and they love not their
lives unto the death this is the very
attitude God is trying to tell his
people this is the attitude you must
have to be able to stand in this time
this is why Psalm 91 beloved is so
significant the Bible says here he that
dwelleth in a secret place of the most
high shall abide under the shadow of the
Almighty I will say of the Lord he is my
refuge and my Fortress my God in him
will I trust surely he shall deliver
thee from the the snare of the father
and from the noise of the pestilence he
shall cover thee with his feathers and
under his wings shalt thou trust his
truth shall be thy shield and thy
buckler Thou shalt not be afraid for the
terror by night nor for the hour that
flies by day nor for the pestilence that
walketh in the darkness nor for the
destruction that wasteth at Noonday A
thousand shall fall at thy right hand
and ten thousand at thy right hand but
it shall not come naively Only With
Thine eye shalt thou behold and see the
reward of the wicked because you have
made the Lord which is your Refuge your
Ark
even the most high by habitation there's
some no evil befall thee neither shall
any plague come nigh thy dwelling
are y'all catching this
I have just a little more to share with
you and then we're going to wrap this up
okay
and for those of you who are in the chat
that are you know that are like no no no
the millennium's on Earth I love you and
I thank you for actually being here and
watching this at least listening even
though you may be chatting at least
you're listening at least you're hearing
oh this is a different perspective than
I've heard before I just want to
encourage you go man search it out like
don't just argue and other like search
it out I appreciate you being here
praise God praise God because the seed
is going to do its work the seed is
going to do its work God needs more
people preaching this because this
message is very unpopular Young
this message is very unpopular
so I want you to check this out
I want you to no there's 800 watching
right now praise God for the all 802 of
you watching right now
amen
amen so
check this out watch this y'all we're
wrapping up I just got a few more verses
okay I need you to understand let me go
back to that last text let me go back to
this text verse 11 for he shall give his
angels charge over thee to keep thee in
all thy ways they shall bear thee up in
their hands lest out Dash thy foot
against the stone Thou shalt tread upon
the lion and the adder the Young Lion
and the dragon shout thou trample Under
Foot I need y'all to catch this y'all
God says you're going to tread Under
Foot trample Under Foot the Dragon
why is that significant if you go back
to Genesis 3 15.
when Adam and Eve sin
and God comes to the garden
because the devil has just deceived them
and God gives the first promise he says
I will put enmity between thee and the
woman between thy seed and her seed it
meaning Christ was to bruise the head of
the serpent trample upon the head of the
serpent trample upon the serpent trample
upon that roaring lion seeking whom he
may devour you will trample upon his
head and thou shall Bruce his heel so I
need you to understand that Jesus Brews
the head of Satan for us but it doesn't
stop there I want to show you how
Hebrews ahead of Satan for us the Bible
says it not before verse 1 then was
Jesus led up of the spirit Into the
Wilderness to be tempted of the devil
and when he had fasted 40 days and 40
nights he was afterward a hunger the
Bible says when the tempter came so the
tempter comes to Jesus in person what's
going to happen to God's people at the
End of Time the tempter Satan is going
to come to them in person but look at
what happens he commanded if thou be the
Son of God commanded these Stones We
Made bread but he answered and said it
is written it is written man shall not
live by bread alone but by every word
that proceeds out of the mouth of God
going on the devil taking them up to the
holy city and set him on a pinnacle in
the temple and send them to him if you
be the Son of God cast yourself down for
it is written
he shall give his angels charge
concerning me didn't we just read that
text and in their hands they shall bear
thee up lest thou at any time Dash thy
foot against the stone notice what Satan
left out he left out the very next verse
you will tread underfoot that the snake
that roaring lion seeking him he may
devour the dragon he left out that text
he don't like that text
Jesus said unto him it is written again
Thou shalt not tempt the Lord thy God
again the devil taking him up into an
exceeding high mountain and showed him
all the kings of the world and the glory
of them and said unto him all these
things will I give thee if thou will
fall down and worship me then save Jesus
unto him get the hand Satan for it is
written Thou shalt Worship the Lord thy
God in him only shout thou serve then
the devil leaveth him and behold Angels
Came to minister unto him I need you to
understand that just as the devil tried
to get Jesus to bow to him
so God's people at the end of time will
come face to face with the Son of
Perdition Satan manifest In the Flesh
pretending to be Christ
and the command will go forth
worship Him
and just like Jesus
just like Shadrach Meshach and Abednego
not doing it will not bow the knee
all right you're not gonna bow we're
about to throw you into a fiery furnace
but not even that matters we're about to
command that you be killed not even that
matters because they love not their
lives unto the death
watch this
watch this I got two more texts two more
I got three more texts and these are
just like one verse okay one verse each
I need you to check this out when did
Jesus ultimately bruise the head of the
servant
at Golgotha
in John 19 17 the Bible says in he that
is Jesus bearing his cross went forth
into a place called a place of a skull
which is called in the Hebrew Golgotha
in the Greek it's Calvary when Jesus
died on the cross when Jesus died on
that skull shaped Hill yes Satan in a
sense bruised his heel but Jesus in a
way more powerful sense
penetrated the head the skull of that
old serpent the Dragon
when that cross was being hammered down
into that skull-shaped Hill that was the
sign of victory that Satan would brew
that Jesus Brews the head of the devil
defeated him on our behalf
but I need you to understand this
because Jesus doesn't leave it there
you know what he's going to do at the
end of time
John 16 20. notice what the text says
notice the promise and the God of Peace
Satan under your feet
shortly wow
wow
so Pastor you mean to tell me
that at the end of time God is going to
use his people Satan is going to come to
God just like he came to God over job
he's going to say I Got the Whole World
in control and God is going to say have
you considered my servants on the earth
and Satan's going to say all right well
let me try everything in my power to
deceive them to get them to Bow and I
bet you I'll get them to bow
the reason why Satan shows up as Jesus
beloved is to try to deceive the people
of God and the rest of the world because
for the rest of the world seeing is
believing oh Jesus really is real okay
I'm Gonna Worship this Jesus not knowing
that it is not Jesus and for the and for
the Christians who are like oh yeah
we've been waiting for the Millennium to
be set up on Earth you're you're
basically literally being set up for
this counterfeit coming
but there will be a people who after
hearing messages like this after
studying the Bible for themselves and be
like wait a minute no no no no this
Rapture thing the way it's taught
popularly no it's not the Left Behind
people uh that are in trouble it's the
ones that are taken because they're
destroyed wait a minute if there's no
Second Coming uh separating seven years
from the the Rapture that's not biblical
that this Millennium happening on Earth
isn't biblical the Earth is in ruins for
the 1 000 years that's why it's
described as a bottomless pit which is
the same description of the earth before
God began creating on it the Earth was
without form and void it's uninhabitable
after Jesus comes and the and the world
is just destroyed and the wicked are
destroyed that's why the righteous are
in heaven because the Earth is
uninhabitable that's why the rights are
in heaven because they're reigning with
Christ a thousand years and at the end
of that Thousand Years the wicked dead
are raised to life to meet their final
judgments Young need to understand this
God is leaving his people here because
he's going to crush Satan under their
feet
he's got to have a witness in the world
you guys
so Satan is coming with this final over
mastering delusion this final assault
before the day of the Lord and God's
people are going to be the ones who
stand firm who refuse to Bow and in
refusing to Bow they're going to Open
the Eyes of other people who are going
to be like wait a minute something is
wrong here this can't be the real Jesus
and beloved
all I'm going to do I'm going to close
with the text
how do God's people overcome at the end
it is very simple they overcame him by
the blood of the lamb and by the word of
their testimony and they loved not their
lies unto the death
that's it
that's all
this is the short version of this study
foreign
this is the short version I pray Joanne
that the 821 people that are watching
between YouTube and Facebook and and uh
and Linkedin I pray
that as y'all have heard this message
today you're gonna go back and you're
going to study everything that you just
heard
absolutely don't take my word for it do
not take my word for it you go back and
study this out yourself and you're gonna
find verses oh wait a minute what about
this verse you got to ask yourself how
does that verse fit in as I said before
a lot of people do not understand
a lot of the book of Isaiah and Jeremiah
and Ezekiel what these prophets were
primarily talking about was the
restoration of Israel for the for the
first coming of Christ and because they
failed those promises never came to pass
those promises are null and void because
they were conditional study these things
out Beloved the Rapture Theory as it is
taught today has its origin
in some place very specific I'm not
going to get into all that now but this
origin this teaching was not always in
the church
so I'm gonna leave it there I'm gonna
plead with you to pray I'm going to
plead with you to study why because our
Salvation depends on it
study to show thyself approved
so let me ask you
if you want to be ready
not only
for the second coming of Jesus
but also ready and prepared to stand
when this counterfeit coming of a
counterfeit Jesus happens I want you to
put a seven in the chat put that seven
in the chat Lord help me to be ready
both for the actual coming of Christ and
for this counterfeit coming where I will
have the confidence the knowledge and
the boldness to stand while everyone
else around me is bowing
praise God
praise God for all this happens praise
God praise God praise God listen share
this share this study all right
share this study far share it wide with
your family with your friends with your
neighbors with your enemies with
everybody
people need to see this they need to
hear this they need to understand this
and if you think you got this study down
and you didn't want to share you know
share this video because you'd rather do
it yourself do it yourself
you want my notes I will send you my
notes I will send you my slide you could
you could sit down and do this
presentation yourself
to whoever you need to do it
all right but God beloved God is doing
everything in his power to open our eyes
so that we may understand the truth and
be ready for what is coming upon this
world
let's be ready for this event amen
amen let's pray heavenly father thank
you for speaking to us
thank you Lord for opening our eyes
thank you Lord even for those who were
watching this study who
have a different understanding they've
been brought up with that understanding
they've studied that understanding and
this is what they think I thank you for
even them watching Lord
I pray that this study will plant seeds
to at least lead some of these lead most
lead all of these people to go back and
study to see if what they have believed
is actually scriptural
Lord bless us help us to be ready not
only for the second coming of Christ but
also for this counterfeit apocalypse
Lord thank you for your love for us
thank you for your mercy for to us thank
you for your grace
in Jesus name we pray
amen and amen I want to thank you all
for jumping on uh thank you for just
fellowshipping with us throughout this
whole day if you didn't see the Sabbath
School I encourage you to go back and
watch that okay
um we have an altar live uh
um after goal the link has just been put
up in the chat so if you want to join us
for the Afterglow discussion please do
so listen the Afterglow discussion is
not for we're not opening the floor for
debate so we don't do that there we for
those of you that were blessed by the
study and you want to join the the
Afterglow and talk about what you
learned please feel free to join us uh
that this is what this Auto live
platform is for so feel free we'll put
the link in the chat feel free to join
us you can you can talk with Fellowship
this is where Community communion really
happens uh with the online church with
the living manner online church so we
welcome you
um and uh we just want to say have a
good rest of your day may you be blessed
and uh may God continue to watch over
each and every one of us
all right blessings to all and we will
see you next week
thank you for worshiping with us today
if this is your first time visiting with
us we invite you to check out our
website at livingmanna.live there you
will learn more about our mission to
reach the world with the Gospel of Jesus
we have exciting live programs
throughout the week covering topics like
physical health mental health prayer
learning how to prove God's existence
and much more if you would like to
support the ministry you can click on
the tithe and offering link on our
website we ask that you continue to pray
for the church as God continues to open
doors for our programming to reach the
world thank you again for your prayers
and your support
foreign